Guide to the Ford Madox Ford collection, [ca. 1850]-1973
Ford, Ford Madox collection,
- Series III. Incoming correspondence and manuscripts by others
  - H
    - Hyde, William ALS to Ford, Dec.6, 1902; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 40)
      Surrey; Dear Hueffer/ Halkett writes this morning asking me to make a drawing for one of his articles [Lamb collection]
    - Hyde, William ALS to Ford, Dec.8, 1902; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 41)
      Surrey; My dear Hueffer/ I received the MS. and your note. I did not send in our stuff to Halkett [Lamb collection]
    - Hyde, William ALS to Ford, Dec.29, 1902; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 42)
      Surrey; My dear Hueffer/ Many thanks for your letter and proposals. I have thought about them [Lamb collection]
    - Hyde, William ALS to Ford, Jan.7, 1903; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 43)
      Surrey; My dear Hueffer/ I am sending today your MS. and four drawings to the PMM. [Leaf torn in half.] [Lamb collection]
    - Hyde, William ALS to Ford, Jan.24, 1903; 2 leaves (Box 70, Folder 44)
      Surrey; My dear Hueffer/ To be quite frank, I am "off" the single article for the pall mall, [Lamb collection]
    - Hyde, William ALS to Ford, Feb.13, 1903; 1 leaf + envelope (Box 70, Folder 45)
      Surrey; My dear Hueffer/ Most kind of you to send me a line, don't bother any more just yet [Lamb collection]
    - Hyde, William ALS to Ford, Feb.14, 1903; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 46)
      Surrey; Dear Hueffer/ I am writing through Kate to save time, & also because I am too angry to write clearly. [Lamb collection]
    - Hyde, William ALS to Ford, Feb.25, 1903; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 47)
      Surrey; Dear Hueffer/ I am sorry to worry you but you must return letters I sent to you [Lamb collection]
    - Hyde, William ALS to Ford, Apr.6, 1903; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 48)
      Surrey; My dear Hueffer/ Thanks for your letter. I am really sosrry that you are having so much trouble. [Lamb collection]
    - Hyde, William ALS to Ford, Sept.26, 1904; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 49)
      Surrey; My dear Hueffer. I am very very sorry to hear your news. [Lamb collection]
    - Hynes, Samuel TLS to Arthur Mizener, May 25, 1969; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 50)
      London; Dear Mr. Mizener/ I have just been looking at some Violet Hunt papers and it occurred to me
    - Hynes, Samuel TLS to Arthur Mizener, Jun.9, 1969; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 51)
      London; Dear Mr. Mizener/ I'm glad you're putting your Rare Book man on to the Violet Hunt papers.
    - Hynes, Samuel TLS to Arthur Mizener, Jun.22, 1969; 1 leaf + 1 leaf + 2 leaves (Box 70, Folder 51.5)
      London; Dear Arthur, (Do you mind the first-name? It will be simpler when they've given us all numbers.) [With TLS to Hynes from A. Colin Cole, April 29, 1969 plus 2 leaves of notes Hynes took at Stones Porter on the Violet Hunt papers there.] [Gift of Arthur and Rosemary Mizener]
    - Hythe Golf Club A & printed D to Ford, Oct.30, 1897; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 52)
      Hythe [Receipt for payment of yearly fees at the Hythe Golf Club]
  - I-L
    - Ingelow, Jean ALS to Margaret Raine Hunt, [n.d.]; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 53)
      [n.p.] Dear Mrs. Hunt/ If the fog keeps off tomorrow I hope to appear - [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Ingelow, Jean ALS to Margaret Raine Hunt, Jan.14, 1884; 1 leaf + envelope (Box 70, Folder 54)
      London; Dear Mrs. Hunt/ Very many thanks for the private cie card - I should have been delighted to use it [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Ingelow, Jean ALS to Margaret Raine Hunt, Jun.7, 1886; 1 leaf + envelope (Box 70, Folder 55)
      London; Dear Mrs. Hunt/ I have been wanting to come & see you ever since you wrote to congratulate you on the pleasant news [Violet Hunt papers]
    - International Labor Defense TLS to Ford, May 9, 1935; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 55)
      New York; Dear Mr. Ford: This is to remind you about the article on the right of asylum [Signed Louis Colman]
    - International Literary Management TLS to Arthur Mizener, Nov.5, 1965; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 56)
      London; Dear Mr. Mizener/ Thank you for your letter of October 3. [Signed by Susan Kellaway]
    - L'Intransigeant TLS to Ford, Sept.4, 1933; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 57)
      Paris; Monsieur/ C'est votre confrere Seabrook qui me donne votre adresse [Signed Hector Ghilini]
    - L'Intransigeant TLS to Ford, Sept.18, 1933; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 58)
      Paris; Monsieur et cher confrère/ Je reçois votre papier et la photo qui l'accompagne
    - J., C. H. ALS to Violet Hunt, Nov.11, 1898; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 59)
      London; Cheer up, little pal. You have some friends. [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Jack, P. A. M. ALS to Ford, Feb.24, 1932; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 60)
      New York; Dear Sir, Thank you so much for your letter which was a great pleasure to me.
    - Jackson, Mrs. Percy, Apr.4, 1921; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 60.5)
      London; My dear Ford/ I am distressed to have been in Berkshire just on the day when you are in town.
    - James, Henry AL[copy]S to Ford, Sept.11, 1896; 2 leaves + 1 leaf + evnelope (Box 70, Folder 61)
      Rye; Dear Sir, I shall be very happy to see you & talk with you -- [Original at Harvard; with typed transcription]
    - James, Henry AL[copy, telegram] to Ford, Sept.14, 1896; 1 leaf + 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 62)
      Rye; Shall be glad to see you at luncheon [Original at Harvard; with typed tanscription]
    - James, Henry AL[copy, ] to Ford, Dec.30, 1897; 2 leaves + 1 leaf + envelope (Box 70, Folder 63)
      London; Dear Mr. Madox Hueffer- Many thanks for your information about Mr. Hyde [Original at Harvard; with typed tanscription]
    - James, Henry TL[copy] to Ford, May 23, 1900; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 64)
      Rye; Dear M.F. Hueffer- I take it very kindly that you have sent me your so curious and interesting book of verses [Original at Harvard]
    - James, Henry AL[copy]S to Ford, May 16, 1901; 4 leaves + 2 leaves + envelope (Box 70, Folder 65)
      Rye; My dear F. M. Hueffer- I am overwhelmed by your letter, touched by your sympathy, and almost appalled by your munificence:[Original at Harvard; with typed transcription]
    - James, Henry AL[copy]S to Ford, Mar.19, 1902; 4 leaves + 1 leaf + envelope (Box 70, Folder 66)
      Torquay; Dear Mr. Hueffer- I am sorry you should be burdened with questions of the order of the one you quote from Garnett [Original at Harvard; with typed transcription]
    - James, Henry AL[copy]S to Ford, Sept.9, 1902; 4 leaves + 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 67)
      Rye; My dear Hueffer- I thank you ever so kindly for your letter which gives me extreme pleasure [Original at Harvard; with typed transcription]
    - James, Henry AL[copy]S to Ford, Oct.26, 1903; 2 leaves + 1 leaf + envelope (Box 70, Folder 68)
      Rye; Dear Hueffer- I ought already to have thanked you for the handsome present of the Romantic volume, [Original at Harvard; with typed transcription]
    - James, Henry TL[copy]S to Ford, Jan.8, 1904; 2 leaves + 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 69)
      Rye; My dear Hueffer- II thank you kindly, even from a prostrate posture which forbids my doing aught [Original at Harvard; with typed transcription]
    - James, Henry AL[copy, fragment]S to Ford, [Apr., 1904]; 2 leaves + envelope (Box 70, Folder 70)
      London; ... I can't begin to "think of" my book for at least a year [Original at Harvard]
    - James, Henry AL[copy, fragment]S to Ford, Apr.14, [1904]; 2 leaves + 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 71)
      London; My dear Hueffer- Lord bless you, it is allright about your book of which I am delighted to hear [Original at Harvard; with typed transcription]
    - James, Henry AL[copy]S to Ford, Mar.17, [1906]; 2 leaves + 2 leaves + 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 72)
      London; My dear Hueffer- I write to Conyers Carr by this post -- & as in a period of 30 years [Original at Harvard; with typed transcription]
    - James, Henry AL[copy]S to Ford, Oct.10, 1907; 2 leaves + 1 leaf + envelope (Box 70, Folder 73)
      Rye; Dear Ford Hueffer- Just a word to say that I hope very much you will come down for your Winchelsea books [Original at Harvard; with typed transcription]
    - James, Henry TL[copy]S to Ford, [1908?]; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 74)
      London; My dear Hueffer- I am delighted to hear that your novel announces itself as Epoch-making [Typed transcription; original at Harvard]
    - James, Henry TL[copy] to Ford, Nov.8, 1909; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 75)
      Rye; Dear Ford Hueffer. very pressing occupation has to this moment prevent my writing you [Typed copy] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - James, Henry TL[copy]S to Ford, Nov.8, 1909; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 76)
      Rye; Dear Ford Hueffer. Very pessing occupation has prvented till this moment my writing you [Typed transcription]
    - James, Henry AL[copy]S to Elsie Martindale Hueffer, Sept.18, 1903; 2 leaves +1 leaf + envelope (Box 70, Folder 77)
      Rye; Mrs. Hueffer- Most kind you note & most tempting your invitation [Typed transcription; original at Harvard]
    - James, Henry AL[copy]S to Elsie Martindale Hueffer, Feb.19, 1904; 1 leaf + 1 leaf + envelope (Box 70, Folder 78)
      London; Dear Mrs. Hueffer- On Thursday 25th with great pleasure [Typed transcription; original at Harvard]
    - James, Henry AL[copy]S to Elsie Martindale Hueffer, Feb.20, 1904; 2 leaves + 1 leaf + envelope (Box 70, Folder 79)
      London; Dear Mrs. Hueffer- If you kindly mean to dinner on this coming Thursday [Typed transcription; original at Harvard]
    - James, Henry AL[copy]S to Elsie Martindale Hueffer, Feb.25, 1904; 2 leaves + 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 80)
      London; Dear Mrs. Hueffer- I have both you sad letter and Hueffer's telegram [With typed transcription; original at Harvard]
    - James, Henry AL[copy]S to Elsie Martindale Hueffer, Mar.22, 1904; 2 leaves +1 leaf + envelope (Box 70, Folder 81)
      London; Dear Mrs. Hueffer- Your remembrance of me is very kind & I accept with pleasure the ticket [With typed transcription; original at Harvard]
    - James, Henry TL[copy]S to Elsie Martindale Hueffer, Aug.11, 1904; 2 leaves + 2 leaves + envelope (Box 70, Folder 82)
      Rye; Dear Mrs. Ford Madox- Oh yes, I must acknowledge your interesting and touching letter, for which I thank you. [With typed transcription; original at Harvard]
    - James, Henry AL[copy]S to Elsie Martindale Hueffer, Jan.23, 1906; 1 leaf + 1 leaf + envelope (Box 70, Folder 83)
      Rye; Dear Mrs. Hueffer- All thanks for the kind documentary evidence. [With typed transcription; original at Harvard]
    - James, Henry AL[copy]S to Elsie Martindale Hueffer, Feb.19, 1904; 1 leaf + 1 leaf + envelope (Box 70, Folder 84)
      Rye; Dear Mrs. Hueffer- I go up to town to stay on Feb. 5th & I go up tomorrow to a melancholy funeral [With typed transcription; original at Harvard]
    - James, Henry AL[copy]S to Elsie Martindale Hueffer, Jul.12, 1908; 4 leaves + 2 leaves (Box 70, Folder 85)
      Rye; Dear Mrs. Hueffer- I am very glad indeed to hear from you, in spite of your sad history [With typed transcription; original at Harvard]
    - James, Henry TL[copy]S to Elsie Martindale Hueffer, Feb.19, 1904; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 86)
      Rye; Dear Mrs. Hueffer- I have already delayed too long to acknowledge your handsome novel [Typed transcription]
    - James, Henry TL[copy] to Violet Hunt, Oct.31, 1909; 2 leaves (Box 70, Folder 87)
      Rye; My dear Violet, Yes indeed I am at Rye- where else should I be? For I am here pretty well always and ever[Violet Hunt papers]
    - James, Henry TL[copy] to Violet Hunt, Nov.2, 1909; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 88)
      Rye; Dear Violet Hunt. I should be writing to you tonight to say that it would give me great pleasure [Violet Hunt papers]
    - James, Henry TL[copy] to Violet Hunt, Nov.2, 1909; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 89)
      Rye; Dear Violet Hunt. I should be writing to you tonight to say that it would give me great pleasure [Typed transcription]
    - James, Henry TL[copy] to Violet Hunt, Nov.5, 1909; 2 leaves (Box 70, Folder 90)
      Rye; Dear Violet Hunt. I am obliged to you for your letter of Wednesday last, but, with all due consideration for it [Violet Hunt papers]
    - James, Henry TL[copy] to Violet Hunt, Nov.5, 1909; 2 leaves (Box 70, Folder 91)
      Rye; Dear Violet Hunt. I am obliged to you for your letter of Wednesday last, but, with all due consideration for it [Typed transcription]
    - James, Louisa Wallace ALS to Violet Hunt, Dec.25, 1934; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 92)
      Rye; Dear Miss Hunt, If I may so address you! How nice of you to say in your letter of last October "do write again." [Violet Hunt papers]
    - James, Louisa Wallace ALS to Violet Hunt, Jan.21, 1935; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 93)
      Haddington, Scotland; Dear Miss Hunt, Alas, I can do little to help you beyond sending the enclosed cutting from todays Glasgow Herald. [Violet Hunt papers]
    - James, Henry TL[copy] to Violet Hunt, Apr.14, 1935; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 94)
      Haddington, Scotland; Dear Miss Hunt, If you are not too busy do tell me if you ever met my beloved author George Meredith [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Jameson, Lena ALS to Polly Taylor, [n.d.]; 2 leaves + envelope (Box 70, Folder 95)
      London; Polly Taylor. Lena Jameson. Let me know your address. I will not give it to anyone [ With draft] [Lamb collection]
    - Jarchow, M. E. ALS to Arthur Mizener, Apr.4, 1971; 2 leaves + envelope (Box 70, Folder 96)
      Northfield; Dear Arthur- What a thrill it was to see "The Saddes Story: A Biography of Ford Madox Ford"
    - Jason, Mark TLS to Ford, Oct.8, 1934; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 97)
      Albany; Dear Mr. Ford- Many thanks for your very kind letter. I am sending you a copy of my quarterly
    - Jason, Mark ALS to Ford, Nov.12, 1934; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 98)
      Albany; Dear Mr. Ford- I was extremely pleased to receive your letter (even though you have forgotten my name)
    - Jepson, Edgar Alfred TLS to Ford, May 11, 1923; 2 leaves (Box 70, Folder 99)
      London; My dear Ford/ It is indeed delightful news that "The Marsden Case" is on its way to me.
    - Jepson, Edgar Alfred ALS to Violet Hunt, Oct.6, 1919; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 100)
      Sussex; Dear Violet, The Lond Brighton & South Coast seems doubtful about when it will have its normal service going again.
    - Jerome, Ann ALS to Ford, [193-?]; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 101)
      [n.p.] Dear Mr. Ford: I have just heard your "speech" on the radio - and cannot let it pass
    - ?, Johanna AL[postcard]S to Katherine Hueffer Lamb, Jan.2, 1906; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 102)
      Germany; 8 Girdles Rd.[Lamb Collection]
    - John, Gwen ALS to Stella Bowen, [Mar.6, 1924?]; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 103)
      Meudon, France; Dear Mrs. Ford, I have received your letter all right.
    - John, Gwen ALS to Stella Bowen, Mar.16, 1924; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 104)
      Meudon, France; Dear Mrs. Ford, Thank you for the transatlantics. I am pleased with my drawings
    - Johnson, F. W. ALS to Ford, May 5, [n.y.]; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 105)
      New Ulm, Minn.; Dear Sir- I have written you on one or more occasions
    - Johnson, Richard A. ALS to Arthur Mizener, Apr.9, [1971]; 1 leaf + envelope (Box 70, Folder 106)
      South Hadley; Dear Arthur, This, briefly, to congratulate you - with awe and admiration
    - No folder 107, 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 107)
    - Johnston, Sir Harry Hamilton, Sept.28, 1904; 1 leaf + envelope (Box 70, Folder 108)
      London; Dear Miss Hunt, I duly received yesterday your new novel "Sooner or Later"-- I shall read it carefully. [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Joseh, Gladys Mulock Hunt ALS to Gerald W. Henderson, May 19, 1937; 1 leaf + envelope (Box 70, Folder 109)
      London; Dear Sir/ Many thanks for your letter of 18th in reply to mine [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Joseh, Gladys Mulock Hunt ALS to Gerald W. Henderson, Jun.16, 1937; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 110)
      London; Dear Sir, Thank you for sending me your notes about the Light of the World. [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Joseh, Gladys Mulock Hunt ALS to Gerald W. Henderson, Jun.21, [1937]; 2 leaves (Box 70, Folder 111)
      London; Dear Mr. Henderson, It is exceedingly kind of you to send me further information [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Joseph, Gladys Mulock Hunt ALS to W. R. Matthews, Dean of St. Paul's Cathedral, May 2, 1937; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 112)
      London; Very Reverend Sir, I am making a catalogue raisonnée of the works of William Holman - [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Joseph, Nannine TLS to Ford, Aug.2, 1938; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 113)
      New York; Dear Mr. Ford: Was sorry not to have seen you to say "goodbye" but I wasn't surprised that you were so tired
    - Joseph, Nannine TLS to Ford, Aug.31, 1938; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 114)
      New York; Dear Mr. Ford: Thank you for yours of the 28th. You confirm what I'd always heard of Don Roberto
    - Joseph, Nannine TLS to Ford, Sept.6, 1938; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 115)
      New York; Dear Mr. Ford: Desperately sorry, but unfortunately I'd already spoken with Dale Warren
    - Joseph, Nannine TLS to Ford, Sept.28, 1938; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 116)
      New York; Dear Mr. Ford: I'm glad to have your new New York address and look forward to seeing you both
    - Joseph, Nannine TLS to Ford, Oct.24, 1938; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 117)
      New York; Dear Mr. Ford: Seeing the announcement in Sunday's Times of the fact you were planning to, surprisingly turn over to the Dial Press
    - Joviens, Mme. Dre AL[postcard] to Edmée van der Noot, [n.d.]; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 118)
      [Denmark] Chère Edmée, Ta carte m'a fait bien plaisir [Lamb collection]
    - Joyce, James PM[galley proofs] Work in Progress, [Spring, 1924]; 9 leaves (Box 70, Folder 119)
      [Galley proofs from April, 1924 issue of "Transatlantic Review" which became pp. 383-399 of "Finnegans Wake". Corrections in Joyce's hand.]
    - Joyce, James ALS to Ford, Jan.10, 1923; 1 leaf + envelope (Box 70, Folder 120)
      Paris; Dear Hueffer: The name and address of the Nice doctor are: M.A. Colin
    - Joyce, James AL[postcard]S to Ford, Dec.13, 1923; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 121)
      Paris; Dear Ford: When sending me the T R could you let me have also the October "Criterion"
    - Joyce, James AL[postcard]S to Ford, Dec.17, 1923; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 122)
      Paris; Dear Ford: Thanks for T R. Can you let me have the Criterion in a few days?
    - Joyce, James ALS to Ford, Feb.25, 1924; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 123)
      Paris; Dear Ford: As it is already the 25th can you please let me have my typescript back
    - Joyce, James ALS to Ford, [Spring, 1924]; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 124)
      Paris; Dear Ford: The proof (sent me without the former one to check it by!) is quite impossible
    - Joyce, James ALS to Ford, Mar.14, 1924; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 125)
      Paris; Dear Ford: Thanks for your note and for the trouble Mrs. Ford and yourself took
    - Joyce, James ALS to Ford, Apr.8, 1924; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 126)
      Paris; Dear Ford: Many thanks for the kind mention of me in Sunday's "Chicago Tribune."
    - Joyce, James ALS to Ford, Oct.10, 1932; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 127)
      Nice; Dear Ford: Your letter has gone round half Europe and here I am beside you almost.
    - Kahn, Otto H TLS to Ford, Dec.14, 1927; 2 leaves (Box 70, Folder 128)
      New York; Dear Mr. Ford: I am in receipt of your letter of the 13th of December.
    - Kahn, Otto H TLS to Ford, Dec.15, 1927; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 129)
      Dear Mr. Ford: I have just spoken over the telephone to the Theatre Guild people
    - Kahn, Otto H TLS to Ford, Dec.24, 1927; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 130)
      New York; Dear Mr. Ford: I am in receipt of your letter of the 23rd of December.
    - Kahn, Otto H TL[telegram]S to Ford, [1933?]; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 131)
      [aboard the DeGrasse?] Sould have like very much to comply with your suggestion
    - Karl, Frederick R. Printed T "Conrad, Ford, and the Novel", [Fall, 1969]; 9 leaves (Box 70, Folder 132)
      [Tearsheets from the Autumn, 1969 issue, pages 17-34 of "Midway"]
    - Karl, Frederick R. TLS to Arthur Mizener, Apr.2, 1965; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 133)
      New York; Dear Professor Mizener: I am editing the letters of Joseph Conrad and for several years now I have been trying to establish
    - Karl, Frederick R. TLS to Arthur Mizener, Apr.9, 1965; 1 leaf + 3 leaves + envelope (Box 70, Folder 134)
      New York; Dear Professor Mizener: Thank you for your long letter about Mrs. Lamb.
    - Karl, Frederick R. TLS to Arthur Mizener, Apr.16, 1965; 1 leaf + 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 135)
      New York; Dear Professor Mizener: As a follow-up on my letter I was checking through Goldring's book
    - Karl, Frederick R. TLS to Arthur Mizener, Jun.7, 1965; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 136)
      New York; Dear Professor Mizener: Thank you for the Marjorie Wynne material from Yale
    - Karl, Frederick R. TLS to Arthur Mizener, Aug.5, 1965; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 137)
      New York; Dear Professor Mizener: Just a short note in answer to your letter of August 2.
    - Karl, Frederick R. TLS to Arthur Mizener, Oct.23, 1965; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 138)
      Caen; Dear Professor Mizener: Just a note to tell you that I will probably be visiting Mrs. Lamb from November 11th on --
    - Karl, Frederick R. TLS to Arthur Mizener, Nov.18, 1965; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 139)
      Caen; Dear Professor Mizener: Thank you for your letter, which I received at Mrs. Lamb's.
    - Karl, Frederick R. TLS to Arthur Mizener, Feb.11, 1966; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 140)
      Caen; Dear Professor Mizener: My relationship with the Universityof Texas Library has become somewhat delicate
    - Karl, Frederick R. TLS to Arthur Mizener, May 10, 1966; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 141)
      Caen; Dear Arthur, That's a good idea about using first names. I've been in France so long that I'm becoming formal.
    - Karl, Frederick R. TLS to Arthur Mizener, Oct.8, 1966; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 142)
      Rome; Dear Arthur, I decided to put my year in Caen behind me and spend this year in Rome.
    - Karl, Frederick R. TLS to Arthur Mizener, Jan.3, 1967; 1 leaf + envelope (Box 70, Folder 143)
      Rome; Dear Arthur, I was pleased to see that you order your shoes from Chipp in New York
    - Karl, Frederick R. TLS to Arthur Mizener, Feb.28, 1967; 1 leaf + envelope (Box 70, Folder 144)
      Rome; Dear Arthur, The news of the Cornell acquisition is marvelous. How much of it I have
    - Karl, Frederick R. TLS to Arthur Mizener, Apr.6, 1967; 3 leaves (Box 70, Folder 145)
      Rome; Dear Arthur, Unless my limited files are deceiving me, your list of Conrad-Ford letters is a bonanza
    - Karl, Frederick R. TLS to Arthur Mizener, Apr.25, 1967; 1 leaf + envelope (Box 70, Folder 146)
      Rome; Dear Arthur,The Ford packet arrived yesterday and thank you indeed.
    - Karl, Frederick R. TLS to Arthur Mizener, Mar.17, 1968; 1 leaf + envelope + 9 leaves (Box 70, Folder 147)
      Rome; Dear Arthur, Did you see that John D. Gordan of the Berg Collection died last week [Included is Karl's article "Picaresque and the American Experience", from "The Yale Review", 1968, pp. 196-212.]
    - Kaufmann, Bella AL[postcard] to Ford, Jan.10, 1905; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 148)
      Basel; Dear Uncle: A happy new year and many thanks for your dear card. [Lamb collection]
    - Kaufmann, Bella AL[postcard] to Ford, Jan.1, 1906; 1 leaf (Box 70, Folder 149)
      Basel; Lieber Vetter, Ihnen und den werthen Ihrigen sended wir innigen Gluckswunsche zum neuen Jahr! [Lamb collection]
    - Kaye-Smith, Sheila Envelope to Violet Hunt, Apr.8, 1926; envelope (Box 70, Folder 150)
      London [Envelope addressed to Mrs. Hueffer in Folkestone, Kent.] [ Violet Hunt papers]
    - Keating, George T. TLS to Ford, Sept.21, 1927; 1 leaf (Box 71, Folder .5)
      New York; My dear Ford:- I was very glad to receive yours of the 19th [Julian Loewe papers]